Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 582, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Hotel Employers Association of San Francisco and Service Employees Union, Local No. 14, AFL-CIO, CLC: Effective August 11, 1980 to August 11, 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 582, Folder 2)
    Author: Hotel Employers Association of San Francisco; SEIU (Service Employees International Union)
  - Item 6: Agreement between General Services employees Union, S.E.I.U., Local 200, AFL-CIO and Community Workshop, Inc.: April 30, 1984 to December 31, 1986, 1984-1986 (Box 582, Folder 2)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Community Workshop, Inc.
  - Item 7: Collective bargaining agreement between Loretto Geriatric Center and Local 200A, S.E.I.U.: June 1, 1991 - May 31, 1994, 1991- 1994 (Box 582, Folder 2)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Loretto Geriatric Center (Syracuse, N.Y.)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 582, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Massachusetts Institute of Technology for its Physical Plant, Dormitories, and Medical and the Service Employees' International Union, Local 254, affiliated with the AFL- CIO: 1981-1983 (Box 582, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: A guide to the labor agreement between the members of Local 200A, SEIU, AFL-CIO and Lakeside Nursing Home: April 1, 1991 through April 1, 1993, 1991-1993 (Box 582, Folder 3)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Lakeside Nursing Home
  - Item 3: Mercy Center for Health Services and Local 721, Service Employees' International Union, AFL-CIO, collective bargaining agreement, Licensed Practical Nurses and Technicians: 7/1/92 - 6/30/94, 1992-1994 (Box 582, Folder 3)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Mercy Center for Health Services
  - Item 4: Agreement between Hotel Employers Association of San Francisco and Service Employees International Union, Local No. 14, AFL-CIO, CLC: Effective August 11, 1980 to August 11, 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 582, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Hotel Employers Association of San Francisco and Service Employees International Union, Local No. 14, AFL-CIO, CLC: Effective August 11, 1980 to August 11, 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 582, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: 1982-1984 Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement (Box 582, Folder 3)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union)
  - Item 7: Collective bargaining agreement between Potsdam Nursing Home and Local 200A, S.E.I.U., AFL-CIO: January 1, 1992 - December 31, 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 582, Folder 3)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Potsdam Nursing Home
  - Item 8: Agreement between the Massachusetts Institute of Technology for its Physical Plant, Dormitories, and Medical and Athletic Employees, the Service Employees International Union, Local 254, affiliated with the AFL-CIO: 1991-1993 (Box 582, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Agreement between the Massachusetts Institute of Technology for its Physical Plant, Dormitories, Medical, and Athletic Employees and the Service Employees International Union, Local 254, affiliated with the AFL-CIO: 1993-1995 (Box 582, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Collective bargaining agreement between Plaza Nursing Home Company, Inc. and Local 200A, S.E.I.U., AFL-CIO: June 1, 1991 - May 31, 1994, 1991-1994 (Box 582, Folder 3)
    Author: Plaza Nursing Home Company, Inc.; SEIU (Service Employees International Union)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 582, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Collective bargaining agreement between Bethany House and Local 200A, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, CLC: January 1, 1992 - January 21, 1995, 1992-1995 (Box 582, Folder 4)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Bethany House
  - Item 2: Collective bargaining agreement between Community Memorial Hospital and Local 200A, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO, CLC: July 1, 1990 until July 1, 1993, 1990-1993 (Box 582, Folder 4)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Community Memorial Hospital
  - Item 3: Collective bargaining agreement between Corning Hospital/Founders Pavilion and Service Employees International Union, Local 200A, AFL-CIO, CLC, LPN/Technical Unit: Expires June 30, 1997, Publication (Box 582, Folder 4)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Corning Hospital
  - Item 4: Collective bargaining agreement between Loretto Geriatric Center and Local 200A, S.E.I.U.: June 1, 1991 - May 31, 1994, 1991- 1994 (Box 582, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: A guide to the labor agreement between the members of Local 200A, SEIU, AFL-CIO and Lakeside Nursing Home: April 1, 1991 through April 1, 1993, 1991-1993 (Box 582, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Collective bargaining agreement between Home Aides of Central New York and Local 200A, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO: August 9, 1992 to August 8, 1995, 1992-1995 (Box 582, Folder 4)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Home Aides of Central New York
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 582, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Collective bargaining agreement between General Service Employees' Union S.E.I.U., Local 200, AFL-CIO and Gateway Community Industries, Inc.: February 3, 1983 to December 31, 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 582, Folder 5)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Gateway Community Industries, Inc.
  - Item 2: Agreement between Local 200, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO and Plaza Nursing Home Company, Inc.: September 8, 1976 to September 8, 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 582, Folder 5)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Plaza Nursing Home Company, Inc.
  - Item 3: Agreement between Local 200, Service Employees International Union, AFL-CIO and Jewish Home of Central New York, Inc.: August 1, 1977 to August 1, 1980, 1977-1980 (Box 582, Folder 5)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Jewish Home of Central New York, Inc.
  - Item 4: Agreement between Crouse-Irving Memorial Hospital, Inc. and General Service Employees Union, S.E.I.U., Service and Maintenance Unit: Expires: December 31, 1982, Publication (Box 582, Folder 5)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union); Crouse-Irving Memorial Hospital, Inc.
  - Item 5: Agreement between the Massachusetts Institute of Technology for its Physical Plant, Dormitories, and Medical, and Athletic Employees and the Service Employees International Union, Local 254, affiliated with the AFL-CIO: 1989-1991 (Box 582, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Agreement between New York City, Taxi Drivers Union, Local 3036, AFL-CIO and member companies of Metropolitan Taxicab, Board of Trade, Inc.: Effective dates: Nov. 17, 1976 to Nov. 16, 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 582, Folder 5)
    Author: Metropolitan Taxicab, Board of Trade, Inc.; New York (N.Y.). Taxi Drivers Union. Local 3036
  - Item 7: Agreement between New York City, Taxi Drivers Union, Local 3036, AFL-CIO and member companies of Metropolitan Taxicab, Board of Trade: Effective dates: Nov. 17, 1973 to Nov. 16, 1976, 1973-1976 (Box 582, Folder 5)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 583, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1988; Publication (Box 583, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Constitution and Bylaws, 1988; Publication (Box 583, Folder 1)
    Notes: UMI Print-On-Demand. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Constitution and Bylaws, 1988; Publication (Box 583, Folder 1)
    Notes: UMI Print-On-Demand. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Constitution and Bylaws, 1992; Publication (Box 583, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Constitution and Bylaws, 1992; Publication (Box 583, Folder 1)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 583, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report number 6 -- School trends (statistics), 1983; Publication (Box 583, Folder 2)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Research Department
  - Item 2: Report number 9 -- Clerical School Contract Survey (statistics), Publication (Box 583, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Report numbers 1 -- School contract survey (statistics), 1982; Publication (Box 583, Folder 2)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 583, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Union Democracy, Publication (Box 583, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: It's your right to have a union!, Publication (Box 583, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Let's talk cents about SEIU Union dues, Publication (Box 583, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The Honest Worker - "SEIU seizes our union", 1985; Publication (Box 583, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: The Honest Worker - "Local 200 President arrested", 1985; Publication (Box 583, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.3 (1985:May)
  - Item 6: SEIU wins best contract in hospital history, Publication (Box 583, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Move the message: an SEIU Public Relations Manual, Publication (Box 583, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: SEIU: Healthcare Benefits Bargaining Guide: Overview of cost containment programs that preserve or expand benefits, Publication (Box 583, Folder 3)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 583, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employer-Paid Health Insurance is disappearing: a survey of benefit takeaways in contract bargaining, 1989; Publication (Box 583, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: In Unity, Strength: Service Employees International Unon, 1985; Publication (Box 583, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The AIDS book: information for workers, 1986; Publication (Box 583, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Massachusetts Institute of Technology for its Lincoln Laboratory and Haystack Units and the Service Employees International Union, Local 254, affiliated with the AFL- CIO, 1993; Publication (Box 583, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Steward manual, Publication (Box 583, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Labor & Management: on a collision course over health care: a study by, 1990; Publication (Box 583, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Labor & Management: on a collision course over health care: a study by, 1990; Publication (Box 583, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: What every school worker should know about asbestos, Publication (Box 583, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: What every school worker should know about asbestos, Publication (Box 583, Folder 4)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Your Union News, 1992; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Notes: April/May 1992
  - Item 2: Your Union News, 1992; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Notes: June/July 1992
  - Item 3: Your Union News, 1992; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Notes: Oct./Nov. 1992
  - Item 4: Your Union News, 1992-1993 (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Notes: Dec. 1992/Jan. 1993
  - Item 5: Your Union News, 1993; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Notes: Feb./Mar. 1993
  - Item 6: Your Union News, 1993; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Notes: April/May 1993
  - Item 7: Your Union News, 1993; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Notes: June/July 1993
  - Item 8: Leadership News Update, 1986; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Notes: June/July 1986
  - Item 9: The Mail Box - 3 Minute News, 1993; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Notes: October, 1993.
  - Item 10: In Unity, Strength: Service Employees International Unon, 1985; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: United Public Employees Local 390/400 - VDT Contract Language, City and County of San Francisco, 1983; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Politics is Union business - SEIU voluteers in the Mikulski for Senate Campaign, 1986; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Guidelines for developing leadership in groups, Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Building Services: A Booming Industry: a report, Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Building Services: A Booming Industry: a report, Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: The Mail Box - 3 Minute News, 1993; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Notes: May, 1993.
  - Item 17: Employer-Paid Health Insurance is disappearing: a survey of benefit takeaways in contract bargaining, 1989; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Making the Federal Job Training Act Work for Women: a guide for CLUW Chapters, 1984; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Sex and race discrimination against Los Angeles County Employees: Preliminary Report, 1985; Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Leon J. Davis, foundeer of 1199, 1907-1992: celebrating the life of Leon Davis: We will build our union in his image, Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
    Author: National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 21: Leon J. Davis, foundeer of 1199, 1907-1992: celebrating the life of Leon Davis: We will build our union in his image, Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: Hello, Sister! Hello, Brother!, Publication (Box 583, Folder 5)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 584, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Healthcare cost containment: labor takes a stand, 1983; Publication (Box 584, Folder 1)
    Author: John J. Sweeney
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 584, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Solutions for the new workforce - folder from conference, Publication (Box 584, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Clerical Workers, Publication (Box 584, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Issues for clerical workers: health and safety, Publication (Box 584, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: A new voice for University office workers, Publication (Box 584, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: District 925, Publication (Box 584, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Welcome to District 925, Publication (Box 584, Folder 2)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 584, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: We are sending this letter to trade union activists, 1992; Publication (Box 584, Folder 3)
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 584, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Eastern Journal, 1977; Publication (Box 584, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1977:Oct.)
  - Item 2: Eastern Journal, 1977; Publication (Box 584, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1977:Oct.). Copy 2.
- New York City Taxi Drivers Union Local 3036, Publication (Box 584, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York's Taxi Drivers build Union, 1966; Publication (Box 584, Folder 5)
    Author: Murray Seeger
    Notes: Reprinted from AFL-CIO American Federationist, August 1966.
  - Item 2: Proposed amendments to the taxi drivers union constitution, 1979; Publication (Box 584, Folder 5)
    Author: New York City Taxi Drivers Union Local 3036
    Notes: From Taxi Drivers Voice, April 9, 1979.
  - Item 3: Constitution, Publication (Box 584, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Taxicab Industry, Health and Welfare Fund, Publication (Box 584, Folder 5)
- Western States Service Station Employees Union, Publication (Box 584, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Articles of Agreement between Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Station Employees Union: Anniversary Date April 2, 1975, Publication (Box 584, Folder 6)
    Author: Standard Stations, Inc.; Western States Service Station Employees Union
  - Item 2: Articles of Agreement between Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Station Employees Union: Anniversary Date April 2, 1976, Publication (Box 584, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Articles of Agreement between Chevron U.S.A. Inc. and Western States Service Station Employees Union: Anniversary Date April 2, 1983, Publication (Box 584, Folder 6)
    Author: Chevron U.S.A. Inc.; Western States Service Station Employees Union
  - Item 4: Articles of Agreement between Chevron U.S.A. Inc. and Western States Service Station Employees Union: Anniversary Date April 2, 1984, Publication (Box 584, Folder 6)
- Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, Publication (Box 584, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution and Ritual, 1986; Publication (Box 584, Folder 7)
    Author: Sheet Metal Workers' International Association
  - Item 2: Constitution and Ritual, 1990; Publication (Box 584, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Constitution and Ritual, 1994; Publication (Box 584, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Stabilization agreement of Sheet Metal Industry Fund: SASMI Trust Agreement: SASMI Rules and Regulations: SASMI Summary Plan Description, 1977; Publication (Box 584, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Carrier Corporation and Local Union 527, Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, AFL-CIO: November 2, 1976, Publication (Box 584, Folder 7)
    Author: Sheet Metal Workers' International Association; Carrier Corporation
  - Item 6: Agreement between Carrier Corporation and Local Union 527, Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, AFL-CIO: November 2, 1976, Publication (Box 584, Folder 7)
- Sheet Metal Workers' Internaitonal Association, Publication (Box 584, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Sheet Metal Worker & Apprenticeship training, Publication (Box 584, Folder 8)
    Author: Sheet Metal Workers' Internaitonal Association
  - Item 2: Sheet Metal Workers Launch Program to Help Unemployed Faced with Mortgage Foreclosures, 1983; Publication (Box 584, Folder 8)
    Notes: Press release
  - Item 3: News from SASMI (Stabilization Agreement of the Sheet Metal Industry), 1978; Publication (Box 584, Folder 8)
    Notes: April 1978.
  - Item 4: News from SASMI (Stabilization Agreement of the Sheet Metal Industry), 1978; Publication (Box 584, Folder 8)
    Notes: June 1978.
  - Item 5: News from SASMI (Stabilization Agreement of the Sheet Metal Industry), 1978; Publication (Box 584, Folder 8)
    Notes: August 1978.
  - Item 6: The Construction Industry the issue is survival - speech by Edward J. Carlough, 1972; Publication (Box 584, Folder 8)
    Author: Edward J. Carlough
  - Item 7: Careers in sheet metal, 1974; Publication (Box 584, Folder 8)
    Author: Sheet Metal Workers' International Association; Sheet Metal and Air Conditioning Contractors' National Association (U.S.)
  - Item 8: Careers in sheet metal, 1985; Publication (Box 584, Folder 8)
    Notes: Second edition
- International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 584, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Contract, 1976; Publication (Box 584, Folder 9)
    Author: League of New York Theatres and Producers; International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada
  - Item 2: Working agreement Theatrical Wardrobe Attendants Union, Local 764, IATSE, 1977; Publication (Box 584, Folder 9)
    Author: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada
  - Item 3: Local 644, IATSE, Agreement, 1976; Publication (Box 584, Folder 9)
    Author: International Photographers of the Motion Picture Industries; ABC
  - Item 4: 1976-78 Internationa AllianceStage Employees, Local 644. (photo copy), Publication (Box 584, Folder 9)
- International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 584, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, 1993; Publication (Box 584, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Constitution and By-Laws, 1995; Publication (Box 584, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Constitution and By-Laws, 1995; Publication (Box 584, Folder 10)
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 584, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: 1982-84 Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement, 1982-1984 (Box 584, Folder 11)
    Author: AFSCME
  - Item 2: Attached is our "Report on the Proposed Collective Bargaining Ageement Between the New York City Transit Authority and Locals 154, 983, 1407, and 1655 of District Council 37, AFSCME, 1980; Publication (Box 584, Folder 11)
    Author: Sidney Schwartz
  - Item 3: Attached is our "Report on the Proposed Collective Bargaining Ageement Between the New York City Housing Authority and District Council 37, AFSCME, 1980; Publication (Box 584, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Attached is our "Report on the Proposed Collective Bargaining Ageement Between the City of New York and District Council 37, AFSCME, 1980; Publication (Box 584, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Federation Employment and Guidance Service and the Community and Social Agency Employees' Union, District Council 1707, AFSCME, 1983-1985 (Box 584, Folder 11)
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 585, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Briefing book on major policy issues, fall 1980., Publication (Box 585, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Briefing book on major policy issues, fall 1980., Publication (Box 585, Folder 1)
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 585, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: This agreement entered into by York County Commissioners herein-after referred to as the Employer, and the American Federation, 1972; Publication (Box 585, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreement between the County of York, Pennsylvania and the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, 1972; Publication (Box 585, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Collective bargaining agreement between the County of Will and AFSCME Local 2961, AFL-CIO: b December 1, 1991 - November 30, 1994, 1991-1994 (Box 585, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Collective bargaining agreement: AFSCME AFL-CIO, Local 2478 and the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights: January 31, 1985, Publication (Box 585, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agreement between the United Jewish Appeal of Greater New York and the Community and Social Agency Employees' Union, Local 1707, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO: February 1, 1972 to January 31, 1974, 1972-1974 (Box 585, Folder 2)
    Author: AFSCME; United Jewish Appeal of Greater New York; Community and Social Agency Employees' Union. District Council 1707
  - Item 6: Agreement between Local No. 1668 and Council 25 of the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees' Union, AFL-CIO and Western Michigan University: August 12, 1991- August 12, 1994, 1991-1994 (Box 585, Folder 2)
    Author: AFSCME; Western Michigan University
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 585, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Contract between State of Connecticut and Council 4, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO: Corrections (NP-4) Bargaining Unit: Effective: July 1, 1979, Expiring: June 30, 1982, 1979-1982 (Box 585, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Contract between State of Connecticut and Council 4, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO: Social and Human Services (P-2) Bargaining Unit: Effective: July 1, 1979, Expiring: June 30, 1982, 1979-1982 (Box 585, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the Community and Social Agency Employees Union, District Council 1707, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO and Local 215 thereof and Jewish Association for Services for the Aged: July 1, 1983 through Ju, 1983-1985 (Box 585, Folder 3)
    Author: AFSCME; Community and Social Agency Employees Union
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 585, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Collective bargaining agreement between Kane County, the Sheriff of Kane County and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO (AFSCME), Council 31, on behalf of and with Local 245 for Kane County Seriff's Employee Bargaing Unit, 1992-1994 (Box 585, Folder 4)
    Author: AFSCME; Kane County Seriff's Employee Bargaing Units
  - Item 2: Contract between State of Connecticut and Council 4 AFSCME, Social and Human Services (P-2) Bargaining Unit, 1979- 1982 (Box 585, Folder 4)
    Author: AFSCME, State of Conn.
  - Item 3: Agreement Harvard University and Harvard Union of Clerical and Technical Workers, AFSCME, AFL-CIO: July 1, 1989-June 30, 1992, 1989-1992 (Box 585, Folder 4)
    Author: AFSCME; Harvard University; Harvard Union of Clerical and Technical Workers
  - Item 4: Agreement Harvard University and Harvard Union of Clerical and Technical Workers, AFSCME, AFL-CIO: July 1, 1989-June 30, 1992, 1989-1992 (Box 585, Folder 4)